I'm so worried for that boy.
Joe's gonna be okay.
She was everything to him.
Jack's gonna step up. He's a good man.
But he's never had to be a father before.
I don't think he understands Joe.
How long did Elizabeth work there?
- Five years?
- No, I think it was six.
- What do you think was in the coffin?
- Jesus, shut up.
I'm just saying, 'cause of how she died.
You guys weren't wondering that?
No. I'm eating macaroni salad.
I was wondering about that, too.
I heard it crushed her completely.
Steel beam, those things
weigh a ton. Literally.
I don't know how you guys can eat.
Try a turkey roll and you'll discover how.
Lucy, down!
Get down.
Joe? You seen Joe?
Bet Joe's not gonna
want to do my movie anymore.
Why?
Why do you think why?
The story, it's about the living dead.
- His mother's not a zombie.
- But she's dead, shithead.
- These turkey rolls are pretty good.
- Told you.
- I just want to talk to you, Jack.
- Get him out of here.
- Hey, Dainard.
- Would you just wait a minute? Wait!
- Jack! Jack, just let me...
- No.
Get out!
Hey, Jack!
- I knew this was a mistake.
- Jack, I...
Jack...
Joseph, I'll be home soon.
Oh, my God.
That was the longest day, ever. Here.
- What's this?
- New scene. Check it out.
Detective Hathaway has a wife now?
I don't know.
I think it might make a better movie.
- I need a better story line...
- Hey!
- ...and production value.
- Guys!
Hey, guys.
Martin barfed all over his locker today.
It was the grossest one yet.
- Oh, my God! Shut up!
- I never seen so many colors in my life.
So who's gonna play the wife? Jen?
No way.
I told you what she did with my top hat.
- What wife?
- Alice Dainard.
I was returning that book on
codes and ciphers.
She was in the silent reading section.
And I asked her
if she'd play Hathaway's wife.
Wait.
You talked to Alice Dainard, really?
You're not supposed to talk at all
in the silent reading section.
- Shut up.
- It's for silent reading.
She said "Yes."
We're filming tonight, and she's driving.
Driving? Driving where?
That was a really good zombie murder.
Yeah, but it's not a story yet.
Older kids are entering this film festival,
15 and 16-year-olds,
who have better stories and
cars and production value.
I've got nothing.
- Charles, dinner!
- I'm coming!
There's this article I want you to read.
It explains everything about stories.
I just don't understand
how the wife helps make it a story.
Jesus, this is what I've been explaining.
That scene we're filming tonight,
where the wife is telling the detective
that she's scared for him,
that she loves him.
I can't believe
you talked to Alice Dainard.
- Charles, come on, move it.
- I'm coming!
And wash your hands this time.
So when he investigates
the zombie stuff, you feel something.
You don't want him to die
because they love each other.
That make sense?
Alice Dainard. That's awesome.
- You're impossible.
- Charles! Now!
God, Mom, I'm coming!
- Midnight, okay? Don't forget.
- I won't forget.
Read this.
It's not fair that I can't go to Wendy's.
Every single person will be there,
except me.
Well, then every single person
can tell you how it was.
Move the puzzle, get the napkins.
- Mom...
- It's your turn to babysit.
Why can't I switch with Charles?
Maybe because you crushed
Charles' top hat.
You ever think of that?
Oh, really? Well, guess what?
We're switching.
Oh, really? 'Cause guess what?
No, we're not.
That's enough. Charles, take this
to the table. Benji, time for dinner!
Hey, Joe.
Night, Mrs. Kaznyk.
Take a seat. We have lots of food.
No, I'm okay. Really. Thank you, though.
- Put them at the table.
- See you tomorrow, Charles.
Later days.
There's always a place
for you here, Joe. You know that.
Stop it!
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Dad?
...that possibility with an announcement
that, while it is not likely,
the potential is there
for the ultimate risk of a meltdown
at the Three Mile Island
atomic power plant
outside Harrisburg, Pennsylvania.
Robert Schakne reports
from Washington.
According to the government's top...
Hey.
I'll be out in a minute.
It's a six-week program.
Hands-on training with college coaches.
You'd like it. I know I did.
I thought I was gonna have
the summer for myself.
Well, things
have obviously changed for us.
And it'd be good for you
to spend some time
with kids who don't run around
with cameras and monster make-up.
I have to help Charles finish his movie.
I've got nothing against your friends.
I like your friends.
Except for Cary, who can't seem
to stop lighting things on fire.
You'd like it there.
It's what we both need.
But they offered you
no real proof he was alive.
And you didn't.
The decision was made.
-So leave the past alone, Martha.
- I can't.
Well, how much would
a ton of gold be worth today?
Okay, it's time. Don't get caught. Over.
I won't. Over.
You, my little pretty one,
my pretty one
When you gonna give me
some time, Sharona?
Ooh you make my motor run,
my motor run
Wait, so, guys, people are turning
into zombies
because of the chemical factory, right?
I don't see how the guy
playing Detective Hathaway
can ask where the zombies
are coming from. Jesus.
Well, technically,
Hathaway hasn't even...
Shut up.
- Was that a rock?
- I'm sorry, Smartin.
- It was a Twizzler!
- Hey, where'd it go?
Hey, guys, look.
Guys, look! Guys!
- It's okay, Smartin.
- Shut up.
Hey, Alice.
Joe Lamb?
Yeah.
What the hell's he doing here?
Make-up, sound and special effects.
He's the Deputy's kid!
- So what?
- You knew that?
Charles, I don't have a license.
I can't drive with him.
You want Joe to stay back? I guess...
It's too late!
He's seeing me in the car right now!
You can trust me.
My dad will never know.
I won't tell him anything.
Get in.
So, I wrote a couple new lines.
Can I show you?
- What?
- New lines?
Charles, do I have new lines?
Do you know what'd be great?
Is if you could cry during the scene.
Can you do that?
- I'm impressed.
- No.
You know the first place I'm gonna drive
when I get my license?
- Want one?
- New Castle, Pennsylvania.
Fireworks Capital of America.
Wait, so, I don't have new lines, right?
Because I just learned these.
Guys, there's an electrical outlet
up here.
Of anything, why that?
- Charles!
- Got it.
Charles, man, do I have new lines
or not? Oh, no!
Well, you just lost all your new lines,
Martin.
Guys, this is going to be great!
Get the lights and camera set up
on that end,
we'll shoot this direction first.
Joe, get the mike plugged in
and make sure that
the new batteries are in the camera
- before you do the make-up.
- Okay. Okay.
I took apart two packs of cherry bombs
and I made my own M-80.
Do you want to see it?
Your obsession with fireworks,
and I'm saying this as a friend,
concerns me and my mother.
"Sweetheart, this is my job.
I have no choice.
"It's nothing that you need
to worry about.
"What am I supposed to do,
go to Michigan with you?
- "Sweetheart, this is my job."
- Martin! I wrote a new line.
- What? No.
- What do you mean "no"? It's awesome.
- Okay, so, you know that part when...
- I just finished memorizing this line.
- It's not gonna be hard...
- Do you mind?
- So, you know that part when you say...
- No.
- Well, where'd the other line go?
- It's gone. This one's better.
Here, I'll...
- No, it didn't.
- I've never even had any lines.
- I just needed this one.
- There.
Thanks.
Look, look. Look!
Now I'm not prepared!
Look, it flows better. "Honey, I love you."
"I love you, too." See? It flows.
I know, but you keep changing things
and making it more difficult for me.
It's... Martin, it's simple.
"I love you, too."
It's, like, four words.
My dad works at the mill.
Four words that I don't
have memorized.
Martin. Can you say, "I love you"?
Could you close your eyes, please?
Yeah.
So, the scene is very emotional.
Alice, Mrs. Hathaway really doesn't want
her husband
to keep
investigating these zombie murders.
- Yeah, I know. We read it. We get it.
- You really hate it.
God, I'm just directing.
Martin. Martin, get in position.
You need to reassure her.
Wait. Do you know
what "reassure her" means?
Yeah, I think so.
Okay. We're gonna shoot
on Alice's side first.
Okay, Preston, so,
a few seconds after I say "action,"
I want you to walk over to the pay phone.
You know,
make the place look like it's busy.
- "Hello, hello?"
- I know what that looks like.
Asshole! Could you stop blowing shit up
for two seconds
and deal with the camera?
God. Sorry, man.
Okay, you guys, let's rehearse this.
But remember, save the real
performance for when we're filming.
Here we go. Positions, and action!
So, I'm going to stay here
and investigate.
I think it'd be safer
if you left town for a couple of days.
John, I don't like it.
This case. These murders.
Well, what am I supposed to do,
go to Michigan with you?
Mackinac Island's beautiful
this time of year.
Sweetheart, this is my job.
The dead coming back to life?
- I think you're in danger.
- I have no...
I have no choice.
You do have a choice.
We all do.
John,
I've never asked you to stop.
I've never asked you to give up,
or walk away,
but I'm asking you now.
Please.
For me.
Don't go. Don't leave me.
I need to know this isn't the last time
I'm going to see you.
I just love you so much.
I love you, too.
Was that good?
Yeah. Yeah, that was... That was great.
Production value!
- Cary, you put film in the camera, right?
- I didn't put it in.
What? Put it in, put it in!
Joe, get the mike ready! Go, go, go!
- Get in costume, costume, costume!
- Okay, I will.
Joe, help her! Hurry up!
Martin, get that tripod set up!
- Preston, get in position!
- I will. I have to get the money.
Go! Get these headphones ready!
Martin, you know your lines!
- Hurry! Get that camera ready! Go, go!
- Shut up!
We'll start on Alice and pan
to the train, right?
Oh, God, I hope we don't miss it!
Shut up! I am trying!
Hurry! Get that set up!
Let's go! Positions, positions!
Ready. Start filming.
Be extra loud when the train passes by.
Here we go. And action!
Look, I'm going to stay here
and investigate.
I think it'd be safer
if you left town for a couple of days.
John, I don't like it.
This case. These murders.
What do you want me to do,
go to Michigan with you?
Mackinac Island's beautiful
this time of year.
The dead coming back to life?
I think you're in danger!
I don't have a choice!
You do have a choice!
We all do!
John, I've never asked you to stop!
I've never asked you to give up
or walk away!
But I'm asking you now!
Please, for me,
just don't go!
Just don't go back! Don't leave me!
I need to know this isn't the last time
I'm going to see you!
- I love you so much!
- I love you, too!
- Guys, watch out!
- Joe, what the hell are you...
- Oh, my God!
- Run!
- Go!
Holy shit!
Go, go, go!
Alice!
Joe, let's go! We got to go!
- Keep going!
- Are we alive?
I don't want to die!
Oh, my God!
Subtitle | www.movieddl.me
Guys.
I'm okay.
Martin, you okay?
Though I think I'm having a heart attack.
And I have a scrape.
Joe! Oh, my God!
- Guys, did you see those explosions?
- You guys seen Alice?
That was unbelievable!
- Why did this happen?
- Martin, it's gonna be okay.
No, it's not, dude. Look at this.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
What's all that blood?
What's the blood?
Did someone get hurt?
- Joe, what are you doing?
- Joe, stop!
- Don't put your hand under there!
- Joe, you don't know what's under there!
Joe!
It's my fake blood!
It's fake.
Guys?
- Come here. What are these things?
- Shit.
No one cares! Look around you!
They look like white Rubik's Cubes,
or something.
I don't think that's what they are.
They don't move.
They're heavy, like metal or something.
There's like a billion of them!
What's going on?
- Martin, it's gonna be okay, all right?
- Are you serious?
You guys! Get up here.
You can see everything from up here!
Joe!
According to my Uncle Seth,
an accident like this
is exceptionally rare.
- It wasn't an accident.
- What?
- There was a truck on the train tracks.
- Are you serious?
What, like, driving on the tracks?
There.
Oh, my gosh.
How could a pickup truck
derail a train, man? That's impossible.
Obviously, it isn't.
Holy shit!
Oh, my God. I know that truck.
Guys.
Is that him?
Yeah. It's him.
- Who?
- It is. Yeah, for sure.
Who is it?
Dr. Woodward.
Dr. Woodward, the science guy?
- Biology.
- Honors Biology.
- Wow. I'm not in his class.
- We know.
Just shut up, Cary.
Remember when Old Man Woodward
took your Electronic Football?
Yeah. He put it in the dungeon
and never gave it back.
The dungeon?
That trailer Woodward keeps
in the school parking lot.
Dr. Woodward?
"Map of the Contiguous United States."
What's the writing?
Dates and times.
Guys, what's this line?
It's a schedule for the train.
What the...
He's alive. He's alive!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Holy shit.
Who are you?
Dr. Woodward, it's me.
Charles Kaznyk. From fourth period.
You've been in an accident.
You're gonna be okay.
- Back!
- Holy shit! Holy shit!
They will kill you.
Do not speak of this.
Or else you
and your parents
will die.
Guys, look.
- We shouldn't be here.
- Oh, my God!
- Go!
- Come on!
- Shit! Let's get the hell out of here!
- Holy shit! Run! Shit!
Guys, there are a lot of nails
on the ground. Be careful.
Hurry, come on, guys!
Guys, come on!
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- Holy shit!
Grab the film!
Guys, come on!
Move your ass! Let's go! Let's go!
- Who's got the bags?
- Get in the car!
Get in!
They're getting closer!
Come on!
- Anybody get their plates?
- I didn't get the plate. Did you get it?
All clear.
Holy shit! That was insane!
- He had a gun! An actual physical gun!
- Oh, shit!
My heart is pounding!
That train could've killed us!
Are you okay?
- Oh, shit! My camera's shattered now.
- No.
Guys, I have never had a teacher
aim a gun at me!
It's hard enough to drive
without everyone yelling!
Guys, keep it down.
"You'll die. Your parents will die."
Guys, this is not good information!
Oh, shit! The focus ring just fell off!
No one cares about your camera!
Guys, am I the only one shaking?
And I'm also crying!
We can't tell anyone we were there.
My dad can't find out I took his car.
Do you guys hear me?
It's okay.
We're not saying anything to anyone.
Guys!
We're not saying anything, are we?
- No.
See?
No one's going to know.
No one's saying anything.
Joe.
Thanks.
I never should have done this.
Joe. Joe, wake up.
- Make sure you let Lucy out, all right?
- Okay. I will.
What are you gonna do?
You going to be with Charles today?
Yeah. I'll be with Charles.
All right. I'm heading in.
There's something I got to deal with.
- Don't forget to get the yard.
- I will.
Mom, come on!
No! You are not wearing that.
No one in this house is wearing that.
Oh, really?
Compared to Debbie's, these are long.
Listen to your mother.
So, I can't go to Wendy's party
or wear the shorts? Not fair!
Jennifer Anne, "not fair" is Africa.
Mom's racist!
- Do we have any more English muffins?
- Why don't you get up and check.
- Peg, tell the twins to stop.
- I can't, they don't listen.
- Morning, Joe.
- Good morning, Mr. Kaznyk.
Hey, Joe.
Did you hear about the train crash?
- No.
- It's on the news.
...instead opting to use
military personnel,
which for this reporter
only adds to the mystery.
Of course, we'll have much more
on this story as it develops.
Coming to you live from Montgomery
County, Channel 14 News...
Can you believe this?
No.
- It's on the news, that means it's real.
- I know.
Local teacher Thomas Woodward
is still being treated
by Air Force medical personnel
after last night's train derailment.
Woodward apparently fell asleep
at the wheel of his pickup truck,
which was hit by the speeding train.
- This is gross!
- Well, how about you clean it up?
That would be a great help.
Thanks so much.
...derailment, the largest such accident
in Ohio's history.
The condition of Woodward,
who has taught at Lillian Middle School
for the past six years...
Looks like a disaster movie. Doesn't it?
Oh, my God.
Sit down!
Joe, that's awesome.
- What?
- We can use it. We can film it.
You want to go back?
- Holy shit, that's mint.
- Really?
You're a total brain.
We gotta go get the camera fixed
- and the film developed from last night.
- Okay.
I'm gonna go steal some money
from my mom.
If any of the footage is
usable from last night,
that means we need Alice
to play the wife again.
Oh, yeah. I thought she was really good.
Dude, she was mint,
but she's never gonna do it.
I think she will.
There's no way.
You heard what she said.
Well, that was before
the new scenes, right?
You honestly think she cares about
the scenes? She was totally wigged.
Yeah, she was. We all were.
Lens is cracked.
Focus ring broke.
You think it's fixable?
I think it's cheaper to buy a new one.
The camera's busted, man. It's over.
We can use my dad's camera.
- It's got some...
- Hello?
- Hey, Alice. It's Joe Lamb.
- Hi.
So, we have some new scenes
for the movie
and Charles and I were hoping
you'd be in them.
No. No, I'm done with that.
I need this film developed
as soon as possible.
Can you do overnight?
Asshole, no one can do overnight.
You want to buy some pot?
No. No, thank you.
Well, what's the fastest you can do?
I can make it a rush.
You'll get your film back in three days.
Hey, what's your sister up to?
The hot one, not the other one.
I don't know.
I'm watching the crash on the news.
- Yeah. I saw it.
- I should go.
Wait. Hold on. Let me come over
and I'll bring the scenes...
- No, no. Don't. Don't come...
- I'll be right there. It's a good idea.
I don't care what Charles wants.
I said no on the phone.
You totally did, I know that's true, but...
But now you're at my house.
I am. Which...
I don't understand how you guys can
keep working on that stupid movie.
You should go.
What's this?
He was just inviting me to a party.
- Yeah?
- Good morning, Mr. Dainard.
She's not going to your party.
Yes, sir.
You. Get out of here.
You go home and
you don't come back here!
I don't want to see you.
Ally, come inside!
Ally, I'm in the kitchen.
I'll do it.
What?
Cut! That was mint!
Oh, my God. With the train...
So good!
- Joe, reload the cap gun.
- Okay.
We'll shoot another angle next.
Alice, that was mint.
Martin, go a little faster next time.
I'll try, Charles, but I'm still crying about
last night, man. I feel like I'm crazy.
Guys, did it really look good?
My death?
- Dude, it looked awesome.
- That was magic.
What do you think happened?
You mean why he crashed the train?
I just got a horrible feeling.
Dude, what are you doing?
That whole thing's an Air Force train.
What?
I make models. Like, plastic ones.
You know, glue them, paint them...
- And he's not embarrassed by that.
- Look who's talking, Math Camp!
Thanks. Can I have a coffee, please?
Cream on the side.
- Sure.
- He's so sophisticated.
- Shut up. I like coffee.
- No one likes coffee.
Air Force trains, even the models,
have these hooks...
They do! For when the trains are
loaded on the transport ships.
Every car in that crash had hooks.
Joe, would you stop
talking about it, all right?
Wait, guys.
Am I the only one who doesn't
understand what any of this means?
- Probably, Smartin.
- Cary, shut up.
- You shut up.
- I don't like it when you call me that.
I'm sorry, Smartin.
Let's just go cry about it.
Dr. Woodward had that map.
He drove onto the train tracks.
Maybe there was something
he wanted to...
- To destroy, yeah!
- My God, will you guys just shut up?
Maybe he was just sick of being old
and wanted to kill himself.
That's a dumb idea.
He had a gun. Why not use that?
There are infinitely more effective ways
to commit suicide. Pills, hanging...
Pussy! Stop taking the fries away.
- I ordered these for a reason.
- Excuse me.
Could we get another order of fries?
Because my friend here is fat.
Funny, chompers. At least I don't have
to use a booster seat.
You could jump from a building.
- Or fall down some stairs.
- Well, that's not really effective.
If it's the Air Force, what would
the Air Force have on the train?
Jesus, shut up about it.
You heard what Old Man Woodward
said, we can't talk about this.
Joe, seriously.
Do you really wanna take a chance
that something could happen
to your dad, too?
All right, easy, easy!
- It's loaded. Move out.
- Yes, sir.
Yes, Deputy. I'm told this crash has
caused a whole mess of confusion.
Well, as you can expect,
the local authorities
are trying to figure out just what
happened, as well as how to help you.
It's all under control.
It'll be a very fast clean-up.
Colonel, there isn't anything
that I should know, is there?
Not that I can think of, Deputy.
I understand you have concerns
about our cargo.
Well, I'd like to see that manifest, yes.
Well, that's not gonna be possible.
Colonel, I've got a lot of people
in my town
that are gonna wanna know
what's taking place.
Which town is that?
Lillian.
Deputy, if you're asking me if we had
any dangerous property
on board this train,
I can assure you the answer is "No."
Colonel!
Excuse me.
They gave me the runaround
for two hours
before they allowed me
to talk to anyone.
I'd say they've had their hands full, Jack.
Nelec, the Colonel, refused to
show me the manifest.
He told me they're carrying mostly
airplane parts. I don't buy that.
It's Air Force, Jack.
Airplane parts sort of make sense.
Sheriff, I'm telling you,
there's something else going on.
They're taking molds of tire tracks.
Why would they be doing that?
Who would they be looking for?
And they're packaging these
weird little cubes into these crates.
Weird little cubes?
Yeah, they're loading them onto these
red trucks. There are dozens of them.
Sheriff, I think you need to go
check it out.
And I think you need to take a break.
Jack, I've been telling you this
since Elizabeth.
You're a good deputy,
but you need to take a vacation.
Go home. Take off the uniform.
Go fishing. Give your son a hug.
Hey, Breen, I'm not sure Edie's
paying you to listen to the radio.
Breen!
Hey, Sheriff.
What's that?
Walkman. It's like a stereo.
Play your own cassette tapes.
You want to try?
I don't think so.
Kids walking around with their
own stereos, just what we need.
It's a slippery slope, my friend.
Yes, sir.
Sheriff?
You know, in scene... Where is it?
Where'd you learn to do this?
Mostly the Dick Smith
Monster Make-up Handbook.
Hey, Joe. We need some more
footage of the train crash.
Obviously.
You know that train model
you just made?
- Your cargo train.
- I want to blow it up and film it.
Let me blow it up.
Yeah. Sure.
- Mint!
- Gnarly! Yes!
Here, take this, will you?
It's fine. They can blow it up.
I don't care.
You want to see it? The train?
My train model? The train I made?
Dude, that's bitching.
Dude, that's like the third time
it's happened.
What the hell?
So how am I supposed to be a zombie?
Pretty much just be a lifeless ghoul,
with no soul. Dead eyes.
Scary. Did you ever have Mrs. Mullin?
- For English? Yeah.
- Yeah.
Kind of like her,
but hungry for human flesh.
Like she wants to turn
somebody into a zombie.
'Cause that's kind of what zombies do.
Oh, my God, yeah. That's really good.
Not bad.
- Really?
- Really.
Careful! There was a gas spill.
I don't even know how much fuel I lost.
You don't seem to be asking
very many questions.
Give the man some time, Mr. Blakely.
- He's only a deputy, he's not the Sheriff.
- Doesn't matter.
I think this is most likely a bear attack.
Security cameras showed nothing.
Someone had erased...
Vicky, you heard
from Sheriff Pruitt this morning?
Negative. Still no word.
Vicky, you need to have Dayton
send a C.S. unit out to Edie's,
and you put an A.P.B. out on the Sheriff
and Breen Haskell,
and send units over to their houses
immediately. You copy all that?
Copy. And, Jack,
we're getting a lot of unusual calls.
What kinds of unusual calls?
I've never seen this kind of thing before.
I mean,
what the hell am I supposed to do?
The insurance company guy
thought I was joking with him.
Look at my Bonneville over here!
They'd have to have
a winch to take that out.
You been having any
troubles with anyone lately, Izzy?
Well, I was thinking
you should talk to Louis Dainard.
Yeah. I didn't help him out
with financing last year,
and I wouldn't be surprised if this was
some sort of sick retribution.
- My generator is missing.
- The phones aren't working.
- My dog's gone. Disappeared.
- The phones won't produce a signal.
Call the station and file a report.
I'll have someone come out
and take care of each one of you. Okay?
Lucy!
I got four guys on this case...
People don't feel safe around here.
You know why? Because they're not.
We need to get the National Guard...
Air Force hasn't
answered a damn question.
They've got trucks over at
Woodward's house.
Now, Ben heard they were looking
for Woodward's research.
Research? What the hell?
...shotgun in one of those trucks,
he had, like, a scanner in his hand.
Like a Geiger counter.
They're saying it's just clean up
at the crash site, too,
but they're taking molds of tire tracks.
That means they're looking for
someone. Now what does that mean?
Have you seen Lucy anywhere?
No. I'm sure
she's around somewhere.
I put a couple of slices
in the fridge for you there.
I ate those.
- Sorry, kid.
- Yeah, no problem. I'll find something.
- Hey!
- You got to be kidding.
Pick that up, will you?
Hey, Vicky,
you got power down at the station?
On and off
And Brook County's in the dark.
Do me a favor and get Water & Power
out there right now, will you?
So, the Air Force is looking for a car.
Alice's dad's car.
They're taking tire prints
from the crash site. Over.
I don't want to hear about it.
This is what I've been talking about.
They could be monitoring us right now.
Jesus, shut up. Over.
And the military is at Woodward's house
looking for his research.
Whatever that means.
You cannot flake out on me
and be a dick.
Are you gonna come and
help me tomorrow or not?
I need you to make Alice
a zombie again.
Okay. I'll do the make-up.
Over.
The cables are gone.
All the poles are empty.
Same thing over here in Rose Hill.
Somebody took the damn wires down.
Holy shit!
Hey, Rooney,
you got anything in Lillian?
Hey, Rooney, you copy?
We got a half mile of copper missing.
Lines are back up at M-38.
Truck 14, Rooney's out at the junkyard.
I'll give you an update when I hear back.
I wanna know who took them.
Twenty microwaves
gone from my inventory.
Everywhere you look,
things are going missing.
We've got trains crashing,
people vanishing.
Belmont County's without power.
You know what this feels like to me?
This feels like a Russian invasion.
Debbie, I don't think that the Russians
have anything to do
with what's going on in town.
But I am calling the curfew because
of these exact concerns.
Unless you can tell me who's been
messing around with our stuff,
I say it's the Soviets.
I like you, Jack,
but we need Sheriff Pruitt back.
We've got good people working on that.
Mr. McCandless.
Since Wednesday morning,
my ham radio is a mess!
Some frequencies which I like to scan,
I'm hearing military chatter,
but it's distorted.
And I don't know what it is.
Have you heard that?
Mr. McCandless, can I have a word
with you in private, please?
It was like having my radio hijacked.
I'm sure that must be very annoying.
You don't know those frequencies
offhand, do you?
Sure I do. 13-2-0-1 ...
Patty, why don't you get
in touch with Vicky.
Hey, Dave, you seen Milner?
No, sir. I haven't.
Jack, there's a huge sinkhole
by my garage!
- It sunk almost a foot!
- I'll take care of that.
Hey, Tom. Tom! You seen Milner?
Have you tried his office?
Have I tried his office?
What are you gonna do about the
power? It's been out for two days.
Hey, Rosko.
Rosko. I need you to get
every radio we have
and you tune them to those frequencies.
- Understand?
- No.
- Hey, Milner.
- Yeah.
Don't you have a radio scanner
with a descrambler?
- A voice inverter, yeah, at home.
- Whatever. Get it.
Bring it down here and set it up for me.
Would you please?
- Sure thing.
- Jack, what is this?
I think the Air Force is using
unassigned channels...
Hey. He was at my house
yesterday morning. You aware of that?
We brought him in for the car lot
and other stuff. He's clean.
Well, I'd appreciate it if you'd inform
your son that my house is off-limits.
And so is my daughter.
I think the make-up
was better yesterday.
No, it's good.
I think it looks good.
I should've cleaned up my room.
Did you make all these models?
Yeah. That one is
the Hunchback of Notre Dame.
We watched that one on TV.
This is the train they want to destroy.
Looks real.
It looks so old.
Yeah, that's dry brush technique.
It's when there's a coat of paint
and then you put something
like Euro Gray over it.
Euro Gray?
Oh, my God, there's like
14 different grays. It gets crazy.
What was that necklace?
The one you were holding
at the train crash.
Was it your mom's?
My dad gave it to her the day I was born.
She wears it all the time.
Well, used to.
And...
It was bad how she died and...
But my dad got it back.
Guys, what the hell?
No one knew where you were!
We're here.
- You got to play the soldier.
- I thought you were calling Evan.
Evan blew us off. He's a pussy!
Excuse me.
It's okay.
You got to do it. You're the only one.
Well, what the hell you mean they found
my dog in Brookville?
That's another county over!
Lucy. That's where she is.
I mean, we've got nearly 30 calls
from people who found local dogs,
but the thing is
the calls coming in aren't local.
It's like they all just ran away
in every direction.
This isn't like her,
she just doesn't disappear.
Okay, okay, calm down.
Just tell me what she looks like.
She's got dark hair. It was in rollers.
Do you know what rollers are?
- Yes, I know what rollers are.
- Okay, so...
Hang on.
Negative, unable to recover data.
That's definitely Air Force.
Yeah, it's Air Force,
but what does it mean?
What are they doing transmitting
on these frequencies?
- Maybe it's not even Air Force.
- I bet you five bucks it's Air Force.
- Five bucks?
- Yeah.
We're gonna need units to prepare for
Operation Walking Distance.
What did he say? "Operation" what?
"Walking Distance."
What's this?
He worked at Romero Chemical.
Found out some things
the company was doing.
And after what you told me last night
at the bar, I thought you should know.
Are we gonna get in trouble
for being here?
Production value.
Stop talking about production value.
I think the Air Force is gonna kill us.
- Cary.
- Don't cover my mouth!
We just made this discovery today.
You understand this is top secret?
Of course.
I would never have given you
this information
unless we had worked
together in Vietnam.
- Those were hard times.
- I'd rather not talk about it.
Understood.
- You're a good friend.
- You, too.
Nothing so far.
- How much more is there?
- About 60 more boxes in the basement.
What, more tax returns?
It's here somewhere. We'll find it. If not,
Woodward will tell us where it is.
What the hell is that?
Joe.
Hey, Mr. Lamb.
Get in the car.
Mr. Lamb, that's your camera,
but, technically, that's my film.
What the hell?
Is it me?
I would like to help you out, Deputy,
I really would,
but we operate on
a need-to-know basis.
Why are your trucks sweeping the town?
We will be out of your way shortly.
All right, then I'm sure
you won't mind me contacting D.C.
Talk to some friends about
"Walking Distance."
All right, we'll do it that way.
Deputy! Let's talk.
Just not here.
This is new, all of this,
for the both of us.
Dealing with anything. Just us.
So, I'm gonna make this
as simple and as clear as I can.
You're not friends with Alice Dainard.
When I say "No," I don't mean "Maybe."
I don't mean "Yes."
I mean "No."
I've known Louis Dainard for a lot
of years. He's been nothing but trouble.
Your mother used to say he's
not such a bad guy.
He just needs a chance,
that he was sad.
Well, I tried to be good to him.
And I can't, not anymore.
I will not allow him
or his daughter in this house.
I will not allow you to
spend time with her,
doing projects or whatever it is
that you do. That's it.
I hope we're clear on that.
We're not clear.
What'd you say?
You and I aren't clear about anything.
We couldn't be less clear.
Just because Mom died doesn't mean
you know anything about me. You don't.
You don't know anything about
Alice, either. She's kind.
We're not gonna have this discussion
right now.
- She's nice to me!
- I don't care what she is!
Her father is an irresponsible,
selfish son of a bitch.
You listen to me.
I've got 12,000 people in this town
who are scared out of their mind.
They've got one person to rely on.
It used to be someone else,
but now it's just me.
Move, move!
Let's go. Move!
Deputy, drop your weapons.
Put your hands on the car.
I'm here to see Colonel Nelec!
He told me to meet him here.
You're under military arrest.
Drop your weapons.
Where's Nelec?
I don't want any more trouble, do you?
We've been going through your
belongings, looking for evidence.
What you knew. How you knew it.
Who else might know.
I remember you in the lab.
And I recall we didn't always see
eye to eye,
but that is no excuse
for doing what you did here.
So, in the spirit of moving forward
and avoiding more trouble,
why don't you just tell me
where you put your research
and who else knows about it.
I know you had someone document
the crash that night.
Tell me who that was
and I will help you.
I swear to God on my mother's life,
if you help us now,
we will take care of you.
I've seen what happens, Mr. Nelec,
- when you take care of people.
- It is mine.
He is mine.
I'm gonna bait him and catch him.
He's in me, you know.
As I am in him.
So,
when you see him next,
as I'm sure you will,
I'll be watching you, too.
Are you... Were you sleeping?
Before. Earlier. No.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You want to come in?
Yeah.
Power's still out.
Room's still messy.
I couldn't sleep.
I was thinking.
I wanted to tell you something
before tomorrow.
Don't let Charles blow up your train.
I don't think it's right.
I know he's your friend.
He's so bossy.
But I've known him since kindergarten.
He's really nice.
He shouldn't always get what he wants.
I mean, who always gets
what they want?
I know I don't know you at all.
Even though it sort of feels like I do.
Do you not feel like that?
No. No, I totally do.
I'm just kind of in shock
at this entire conversation.
Power's back.
No, no. Keep it.
It's... It's so weird.
Watching her like this.
Like she's still here.
She used to look at me this way,
like really look,
and I just knew I was there,
that I existed.
He drank that morning.
My dad.
He missed his shift.
Your mom took it for him,
the day of the accident.
He...
He... He wishes...
I know he wishes it was him
instead of her.
And sometimes I do, too.
Don't say that.
He's your dad.
Is... Is this normal?
No. This is new.
Want to tell me where you were?
Or should I tell you?
Sit down.
I should go to bed.
I want to talk to you. I said sit down.
I don't want to sit down!
Then go.
Be just like your mother and leave.
Dad...
Go ahead! Go!
Go!
Alice!
Wait!
Ally, I'm sorry!
Alice!
Ally!
Firelight at 0500 hours.
Operation Walking Distance is in effect.
T-minus four hours to evacuation.
Evacuation in T-minus four hours.
Why are you not reacting?
That thing went through my wall!
I told you not to pick it up
in the first place.
What are you so angry about? That I'm
not gonna let you blow up my train?
That's part of it. Just a part.
Hey. Tell your sister that Donny
from Olsen's broke up with Karen.
That shit ended about a week ago.
What's your problem?
My whole movie's a disaster
because of you.
- I know my dad's being a turkey.
- Whatever.
- We're still gonna finish your movie.
- It's not about the movie.
What are you talking about?
Of course it is!
Just forget it.
Why? There's nothing wrong!
We're gonna finish the movie!
I can get the camera back.
I know where my dad put it.
We can still make the festival.
- It's not about the movie.
- Then what is it about?
Jesus, you don't get it, do you?
It's obvious.
- What's obvious?
- God, you're a dumb-ass.
That night of the crash,
you started getting all weird.
- What? What are you talking about?
- Like Mr. Attitude, all of a sudden.
Your movie was over!
That's what you said! You were upset!
- Oh, my God.
- I gave you a camera! I helped you!
Don't pretend like you did this for me.
You didn't do this for me,
and you know it.
This was never about me.
This was always about Alice!
Action!
I'm going to stay here and investigate.
I think it's safer
if you leave town for a couple of days.
John, I don't like it.
This case. These murders.
Well, what am I supposed to do...
Well, you're the one
who wanted the wife in the movie.
Not so you could fall in love with her.
What do you care
what I think about Alice anyway?
Because I like her!
That's why I asked her to do this thing
in the first place,
so I could get to know her. Not you!
- You like Alice Dainard?
- You're such an idiot!
-Watch out!
- Joe, what the hell are you...
-Oh, my God! Shit!
- Run!
Shit. Look at all that smoke.
I can't use this.
You won't even let me
blow up your train.
Everything's bogus.
We could make another train
and blow that one up.
I do like her.
- Sorry about that.
- Shut up.
It's okay.
That's not even what bothers me.
She likes you, too.
That's what really bothers me.
I know it sounds stupid.
Why would she ever like me?
I haven't leaned out yet
and the doctor says it's gonna happen.
I don't know. Everything's just so bogus.
Charles.
Joe, what the hell?
What is that?
- Mr. Harkin! What's going on?
- Evacuation! The fire!
Wait, wait!
The county is being evacuated due to
a wildfire that is raging out of control,
and threatening to reach
the Lillian chemical plant.
Please take with you
essential items only.
If you are driving your own vehicle,
follow the caravan
to the evacuation center.
Please remain calm.
File in.
File in, please, file in.
- Corporal.
- I left the medication my wife needs.
Sir, the town is sealed off.
No one's allowed in.
- H through N.
- I can't get it anywhere else.
Charles!
Excuse me.
Charles, oh, thank God.
I went back to the house
and you were gone.
Yeah, they put us on the bus.
- Hey, sweetie.
- Hey. I'm gonna find my dad.
- You gonna tell him about that huge...
- Yes.
Come back if you can't find him!
Mr. Dainard, it's Joe Lamb.
I know you don't like me and I'm sorry
about that, but I'm looking for my dad.
It took her.
- It took Alice.
- What?
I saw it. It was big.
And, I don't know, it was something
I've never... I've never...
No one believes me.
They just keep giving me pills and...
I believe you.
That thing took her?
We have to go back to town
to find Alice, to find her. Come on, guys.
- Dude, she's dead. Alice is dead...
- Don't say that!
First of all, I want to live. Okay?
Joe, what do you actually
expect to do, man?
The town's closed.
We're not allowed to go back.
Look, I have an idea.
I'm going whether or not you come,
which I really hope you do.
Come on, guys.
I have six tons of explosives
in this thing.
Let's find that thing and blow it to shit!
As if I'm gonna help you.
Do this for me,
I'll babysit the twins next week,
so you can go to Wendy's stupid party.
I'm not shitting you.
You can't ask me any questions, though,
and you can't tell anyone.
I'm serious. Nobody.
Does it have to be him?
Yes or no, you ugly freak!
I'm about to rescind the offer.
This whole evacuation thing's
really freaking me out.
Making me rethink my priorities.
Saw you over here
and thought maybe we could kick back.
We... We totally could.
I asked Charles about you
and he said you're a great guy.
I totally am.
Will you hate me if I start
our relationship by asking a favor?
So, there are rules
to being in my car, okay?
Where the hell are we going, anyway?
We're going to go to the school
and open the trailer
Woodward has in the parking lot.
I bet that...
I bet that's where
he's keeping his research.
Research. What research?
We're gonna learn everything we can
about that thing,
so that we can find it
and that's how we're gonna save Alice.
Come on. Let's go!
Dorks, no shoes on my upholstery.
And no one touches my C.B.
- You got it?
- The dungeon? Are you serious?
Why else are there six padlocks
on the door?
We're going to the school.
Since when did this one
become so bossy?
I don't know.
I got to take a leak! What am
I supposed to do, piss in here?
Thanks for the hospitality.
Am I gonna go in alone,
or are you gonna end up coming with...
...driving your own vehicle,
follow the caravan
to the evacuation center.
If the Air Force has already searched
Woodward's house,
wouldn't they have searched
stuff in the schoolroom, too?
Yeah, man, I was just thinking
about that, too.
Maybe his room, but not the dungeon.
Woodward keeps all kinds
of weird stuff in the dungeon.
Shut up!
So, what kind of music does she like,
your sister?
I don't care. Disco, I guess.
I can get back into disco.
We shouldn't take River Road,
they put a roadblock up.
Dork, I saw it. Observe.
So, what, I just wait here like a douche?
Yes. Thank you so much for doing this.
Do you have a tire iron?
Joe, let me try! Joe, let me try!
God, I hope my Electronic Football
is in there.
Joe, this is impossible, man.
There's no way we can do this.
These things are made like
a bank vault, like a safe.
Professional robbers can't even get in
through these things. They're so...
Shit!
I loosened it for you.
- Guys.
- Look at all this junk!
He's got movies in here.
I can't believe
we're breaking into the school!
Who does that? Nobody does that!
Idiots do that!
Dr. Woodward was dishonorably
discharged from Nellie Air Force Base
in 1963 because of
"subversive conduct," whatever that is.
Charles, check it out.
It's Old Man Woodward.
Back when he was like
Middle-Aged Man Woodward.
He's been tracking this thing
since 1958.
What is this?
It says, "April 8th, 1963 incident."
I don't know.
- Cary!
- What?
We have to find this thing. Come on!
Okay. Sorry.
...told them that this creature
is more sophisticated than any of us,
that his species
is predominantly subterranean.
- Subterranean.
- And that he is being treated
without compassion or respect.
I explained that all he wants
is to rebuild his ship,
a craft made up of those cubes,
a complex shape-shifting alloy.
Remarkable material
that we'll never fully understand.
He has been desperate to reconstitute
his ship since it crashed here in '58.
But instead of giving him the help
he needs, we've held him as a prisoner.
- Guys, it's Dr. Woodward!
- He's been restrained
and experimented upon,
biopsied, and tortured by Nelec.
Through pain and lack of compassion,
we have taught him to hate us all.
We have turned him into an enemy.
I told them I knew these things
because he made contact with me,
that he makes a psychic connection
by touch.
Oh, my God!
- What is that thing?
- What the hell?
- I can't watch this.
- Martin, you're gonna throw up, man.
The moment we made contact,
I understood him, and he me.
What I know is that if we don't change
this and begin helping him,
we will all pay the price.
But Nelec won't listen.
He wasn't trying to kill it.
He'll have me discharged.
He was trying to help it escape.
But I won't give up.
I will do everything in my power
- to set him free.
- Oh, my God.
- You guys hear that?
- Help him rebuild that ship. I won't...
Freeze! Nobody move!
Do not move!
We got positive I.D. here.
It's just a bunch of kids.
Oh, shit.
Search them.
Let me see that.
I rolled those M-80s myself.
- That's right.
- Jesus, Cary, shut up.
You're the Deputy's boy.
No.
Move out!
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Breaker, breaker.
Requesting police backup.
Breaker 1 -9. Is this the police channel?
- Staff Sergeant.
- Hi. How are you doing?
Hey, Mr. Lamb!
Rosko.
Hey. Where the hell have you been?
- What are you wearing?
- Come here.
The Air Force set that fire. They want
the town empty for some reason.
This whole operation,
this whole military operation,
the evacuation, everything, it's all bad.
- We need to find...
- Did you hear about Joe?
Look, dispatch just got
a call on citizens' band.
Joe and some of his friends,
they were grabbed by military personnel
at the middle school.
Preston, you tell me everything,
and I won't throw you in jail.
Yes, sir.
But I think you should look at this first.
Chief Master Sergeant,
Dustoff-03 is 20 minutes out.
Roger that. Perimeter secure. Standing
by on lookout. Prepare to engage.
Teams Kilo-Lima-Mike-November
in position.
Teams Oscar-Foxtrot-Quebec-Romeo
Cocked and locked. Ready to go.
What's going to happen to us?
I think we're gonna die.
Cary, shut up, man.
They wouldn't do that.
I'm not kidding.
I think they're gonna kill us.
They're not gonna kill us.
You know why?
- Why?
- Because we're just...
Hold on!
Was that that thing from the train?
Why are we stopping?
- Why are we stopped?
- Holy shit!
Contact with precious cargo,
three clicks from city center.
Currently heading towards...
- Driver! Can you see anything up there?
- No, sir! Nothing.
What's that gun?
Sako Bolt Action thirty-aught six with...
Okay, we get it.
Those aren't bullets.
He's loading tracking darts.
Here. Tag it.
Yes, sir.
Open the door!
I don't feel good about this.
Sir, is there a particular area
that you'd want me to shoot...
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Help!
Oh, my God!
Get us out of here now!
What other firepower do we have?
- There's a monster out there, Joe!
- What the hell is it?
I got it, sir!
- Guys, the seat belt is killing me!
- Unhook it!
Come on!
This is Nelec. Use the big guns.
Whatever happens to me,
do not let it...
- Joe, open it!
- Open the door!
- It's bolted!
- I want to go home so bad!
Open the door.
- Please, sir.
- Just let us out!
Please open it!
Where are the keys?
Overmyer had them!
Help me! My leg's stuck!
Please, sir, open the door!
Please, open the door!
Another one dead!
Guys, there's broken glass.
Guys!
Martin! Martin!
Let me get on your shoulders. Come on.
Go, go, get up!
- Here we go.
- Go!
- Come on, Joe! You can do it!
- Come on, Joe!
- You can do it, Joe! Let's go.
- Come on!
- You can do it! Come on!
Joe, please! Go!
- Come on. Break the glass, you pussy!
- Come on, Joe! Hit it! Come on!
We got to go!
- Go!
- Come on, guys, hurry!
Come with us. We got some questions
for you. Come on.
- Oh, no. Is she dead?
- Just come with us.
Hey, fellows,
I've got orders from Colonel Nelec
to personally deliver this man
back to base.
- He's all yours, Staff Sergeant.
- Let's go.
What are you doing?
Where are we going?
To find our kids.
Hey, guys! Guys, I found them!
Hey, guys! I found my firecrackers!
Congratulations.
Let's go, guys, they're coming back.
I think we should go. Come on.
Guys, come on.
No. No, look.
You dorks are alive? I thought that...
What the fuck?
Donny. Donny.
We need a ride into town.
Okay, but just so you know,
I'm massively stoned right now.
Do you want me to drive?
- Guys, what was that?
- It sounds like gunshots.
- Joe, where are we going?
- I saw something in the cemetery.
Woodward said it was subterranean.
I think I know where it is.
What the hell is that?
Move the damn car!
- God!
- Joe, turn the car around!
- I can't. There's a tank behind us.
- Holy shit!
- What are they shooting at?
- Guys, we have to run.
Donny! Hey, Donny, wake up!
- He's too stoned!
- Drugs are so bad!
- Why is everyone firing?
- We gotta go!
Guys, come on, hurry!
- This is crazy!
- What is going on?
Look! It just exploded!
Sir! The weapons are misfiring!
All of them!
Surface-to-air! Radar!
It's a mess out here, sir!
Guys! Guys, run!
Come on!
What the hell is this?
Go, Cary, go!
- Jesus!
- Go!
What the hell?
Holy shit!
Why is everyone firing?
Go, come on!
Move ahead!
Oh, my God!
Come on, guys, move!
Did you guys see those explosions?
They were... They were huge!
Oh, my God.
Whose house is this?
It's Kathy's. I got it off the fridge.
Kathy? Yeah, I know her.
Charles, what are you thinking, dude?
That's not yours!
What, I'm thirsty. I'm in a war zone!
- Clear! Clear!
- Come on, move!
Let's go, move out!
- Guys, come on, let's go.
- Where are we going?
To the cemetery. I'm...
Guys, what happened to my leg?
Man, it hurts!
Holy shit, Martin, you've got
a bone sticking out of your leg!
Joe, give me that thing off the curtains!
God!
I've got to go find Alice.
You guys stay here with Martin.
You gonna be okay without me?
Yeah.
- I'm not staying with the girls!
- God, Cary! Shut up!
- Calm down!
- Come on! Come on!
It hurts, Joe!
Okay, this is going to hurt
really bad, okay?
Jesus, Martin, I haven't done it yet!
Just... Just follow me. Just follow me.
I've been following you for the last five
blocks! What are we doing here?
Come on, through these doors.
Help me.
- Help you with what?
- We have to get inside.
Okay, okay. For what?
I'll tell you in a second.
Why is there dirt in these windows?
It's here. Hard on three.
One, two, three.
One, two, three!
- One, two, three! One, two, three!
This... This is scary.
You got any sparklers in there?
Are you kidding me?
Alice is down there.
I came to your house that day
to tell you that
I never meant to hurt anyone.
I swear to God.
I'm sorry, Jack.
About what happened to your wife.
It was an accident.
Joe, I don't understand...
This way.
Why are you so surprised?
I always wear lipstick on my shirt.
- It's Sheriff Pruitt!
- I know.
Cary, look.
There are bodies everywhere.
- What is this?
- We're under the water tower. Look.
She's got to be here.
It's eating a person.
She's here.
Oh, my God. I see her.
Okay.
We're going to use your firecrackers.
I don't think that's gonna hurt him, Joe.
- There's other tunnels.
- So?
I need you to make noise
right here in two minutes.
Make it loud and make it last.
Give me some sparklers.
Make sure you're gone when it blows.
You can't be here. You got to run.
Where are you going?
Come on, Cary.
Alice. Alice. Please, we have to go.
Come on.
Alice! Alice!
Please, come on.
We have to go. Alice!
You're alive! You're alive.
You're alive. Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
What is this? What are you doing here?
I'm just doing the best I can to save you.
How did you know?
Your dad. He told me. He was worried.
And flipping out.
- Really?
- We have to move.
Excuse me?
Where are we?
I left my bag in the car,
and then I went out to the car
to get my bag...
It's been locked up for years.
It's terrified and hungry
and it just wants to go home.
When it touched me, I knew.
I need you to help me
get the Sheriff down.
Follow me this way.
I'll get us out of here.
- Sheriff, we came that way.
- Don't argue with me! Just follow me!
Come on, kids, let's go with the Sheriff.
This way.
Joe!
I told you to get out!
What are you doing here?
I thought this was the way out.
Okay, I tried.
- Hey, Alice, welcome back.
- Hey!
Come on! We got to get out of here...
Guys, hurry!
Come on, go!
She's gone! It took her!
I don't want to be next!
- Go! You don't want to be here! Go!
- Joe, what are you doing?
Ally, what the hell is he doing?
We understand!
But not everyone's horrible.
- No!
- Joe!
Let him down!
I know bad things happen.
Bad things happen.
But you can still live.
You can still live.
Okay, wait a minute.
What?
- Look out!
- Get down! Get down!
What is he doing?
He's making a model.
I got you.
Holy shit!
This is where my friend was attacked.
- By who?
- I've never seen him before.
He looked pale, crazy. He bit my friend.
- Then what happened?
- He was dead.
- And then...
- He got up and walked away?
- How did you know?
- Anything left behind?
Yes, this fell out of the pocket
of the attacker's pocket.
Thank you.
Hello, Mr. President.
I'm Detective Hathaway.
I'm here to discuss some urgent matters
regarding your chemical factory.
Are you referring
to the recent incidents?
Yes, I believe I am.
Tell the chairman I'll call him back.
You have three minutes.
You want to tell me
about those employees?
I was sorry to hear
of their unfortunate accident.
That was no accident!
Did you see the bites on their neck?
Are you suggesting some connection
between my chemical company
and those, those...
Those were zombie attacks!
Romero Chemical has nothing to do
with any such thing.
Then what happens in Building 47?
You wouldn't mind
if I took a look around, would you?
Of course not.
Good day to you, Mr. President.
Good day, Detective.
He knows.
Judith. It's me, your boss.
I need you to buy my wife
a ticket to Michigan.
It's too dangerous for her here.
I just love her so much.
John, I don't like it.
This case. These murders.
Well, what am I supposed to do,
go to Michigan with you?
Mackinac Island's beautiful
this time of year.
Sweetheart, this is my job.
I just love you so much!
I love you, too.
I can't believe
we weren't killed last night.
Okay, now you have to leave town.
No. I'm staying here with you.
I don't know what I would do
if something happened to you.
What if there are survivors down there?
There were no survivors!
Did you see that crash?
Excuse me, sir, were you in the wreck?
That settles it. I'm not going anywhere.
It's been two weeks,
and the murders continue.
This investigation is like no other.
It's putting too much stress on this town
and on my marriage.
Could zombies be real?
Hello? This is Detective Hathaway.
I'll be right over.
- What's happening here?
- A military police investigation.
It was a suicide.
- A suicide? Who was it?
- A former Air Force officer.
Said there was a secret
he couldn't keep any longer.
It says he worked for Dr. Peter Braken?
I never would have given you
this information
if we hadn't served together in Vietnam.
- Those were hard times.
- I'd rather not talk about it.
- Doctor.
- Detective.
I'm here to discuss your involvement
with Romero Chemical?
I was the one that developed
the special compound
to turn all these humans into zombies.
It was supposed to be used
as a military weapon,
but it got out of hand.
So I made this antidote
that will hopefully cure
all of the zombies.
That's incredible!
How much have you made?
Just this one.
Would you like to help me test it
on this innocent victim of my creation?
Honey, I'm home!
Good news. We found a cure
for the zombie infection.
Honey?
Sorry. It didn't work. I wish it worked.
I tried. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
John?
This has been
a Charles Kaznyk production.
We had such a fun time filming
this movie, The Case.
So much fun that I hope you pick it
for the Cleveland International
Super 8 Film Festival.
God!